{
    "id": "cc90910f9c5b423784e1ba37ba8b34ad",
    "title": "Phrases Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He was a man ................................................ great wealth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The principal was an old man ............................................ friendly disposition.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The workers belonged to a tribe dwelling ................................................. the hills.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There I met a boy .............................................. red hair.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Only a man with plenty of money can buy a car ................................................. such beauty and power",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was a young man ............................................... great promise.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He wore a turban made ............................................ gold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ran .................................................. great speed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You can buy it ................................................. all places.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He replied ..................................................... a very rude manner.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}